couponpaste.com 2016-03-15

# Privacy Policy - CouponPaste.com

**CouponPaste.com Privacy Policy**  
**Last Updated: 01/01/13**

**Our Commitment to Your Privacy**  
Your privacy is important to us, and we are committed to respecting the privacy rights of users of the CouponPaste.com services. We have designed this policy to help you understand how we collect and use the information you decide to share, so that you make informed decisions when using the CouponPaste.com services.

If you have any questions concerning this privacy policy, please email us at contact@CouponPaste.com.

**Information We Collect**  
As with most websites, we collect the following two types of information: (1) Personally identifiable information that is voluntarily provided by users (i.e., information that a user provides that allows us to identify and contact that user, such as their name, address or email), and (2) Non-personally identifiable information (e.g., information that is automatically collected such as the type of web browser, IP address, etc., that does not by itself identify a specific individual).

We only collect personally identifiable information that you voluntarily provide to us. If you do not want this information to be collected by us, please do not submit it.

**Account Registration**  
In order to become a registered member of CouponPaste.com, you must register and create an account on CouponPaste.com’s website. In creating an account, you are required to create a password, and provide an e-mail address.

**User Submissions**  
When you use CouponPaste.com, you may perform and store searches and queries and transmit information through various channels. We collect this information so that we can provide you the service and offer personalized features. In most cases, we retain it so that, for instance, you can return to view prior messages you have sent or easily see your contacts list. When you update information, we usually keep a backup copy of the prior version for a reasonable period of time to enable reversion to the prior version of that information.

Additionally, should a user contact CouponPaste.com on their own initiative or respond to a communication from CouponPaste.com, we may collect the information submitted.

Any improper collection or misuse of information provided on CouponPaste.com is a violation of the CouponPaste.com Terms of Use and should be reported to contact@CouponPaste.com.

**Cookies, Log Files and Web Beacons**  
Like most websites, CouponPaste.com uses cookies and web log files to track site usage. A cookie is a tiny data file which resides on your computer which allows CouponPaste.com to recognize you as a user when you return to our site using the same computer and web browser. Like the information you enter at registration or in your profile, cookie and log file data is used to customize your experience on the website. One type of cookie, known as a “persistent” cookie, is set once you’ve logged in to your CouponPaste.com account. The next time you visit the CouponPaste.com website, the persistent cookie will allow us to recognize you as an existing member so that you will not need to log in before using the service. If you log out of the CouponPaste.com website you will need to re-enter your password the next time you visit in order to log in to your account. Another type of cookie, called a “session” cookie, is used to identify a particular visit to the CouponPaste.com website. Session cookies expire after a short time or when you close your web browser.

The cookies we use do not store any personally identifiable information about you. Most browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can modify your browser setting to decline cookies. Please be aware, though, that if you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to sign in or use some of the interactive features offered on our websites.

Like most websites as part of the communication standards on the Internet, we use log files on our servers. These log files store various non-personally identifiable data regarding your visit with us, such as the internet protocol (IP) addresses, information regarding your browser, internet service provider (ISP), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, platform type, and number and identification of clicks. This information is used to analyze overall trends to help us improve the CouponPaste.com services. Additionally, this information may also be used to help diagnose problems with our server, to administer the CouponPaste.com services, or to display the content according to your preferences. This and other anonymous information collected may also be shared with business partners and advertisers on an aggregate and anonymous basis. The linkage between your IP address and your personally identifiable information is never shared with third-parties without your permission or except when required by law.

We also use standard Internet technology such as web beacons to track site usage. Web beacons (also known as clear gifs) are tiny graphics with a unique identifier that function similar to cookies, and are used to track the online movements of web users or to access cookies. Unlike cookies which are stored on the user’s computer hard drive, web beacons are embedded invisibly on the web pages (or in e-mail) and are about the size of the period at the end of this sentence. Web beacons are used to track user navigation and usage patterns on our website, and to inform us as to the effectiveness of our content and/or communications. CouponPaste.com does not and cannot use web beacons to obtain personally identifiable information from your computer. If a user follows a link on CouponPaste.com (or in an email or newsletter from CouponPaste.com) to a third-party website, we may use a cookie or web beacon to assign an anonymous, unique identifier to the user’s browser to track the user’s non-personally identifiable activities on that site, including whether the user clicks on a link, or makes a purchase. If the user re-visits the third-party site directly, we are able to continue to track the user’s non-personally identifiable activities on that site.

These general targets may also be used by ad networks to display targeted ads on other websites as a substitute for random, irrelevant ads. CouponPaste.com NEVER provides personally identifiable information to any advertiser nor any third-party without your express permission.

**Coupon Codes and Links to Merchants**  
When clicking on coupon codes or other links to merchants on the CouponPaste.com site, you will be sent, via a new Web browser window, directly to the merchant’s site to complete your transaction.

**Contests and Survey**  
From time to time, we may offer our members and other visitors the option to participate in contests or surveys. If you would like to participate, we may ask you for contact information, preferences, or other information. Such information is used for purposes such as to conduct research, improve our offerings and services, or award prizes. Our contests may have separate contest rules and we identify how the information that you may supply will be used in each case.

**Children**  
No one under age 18 is eligible to use our services, and we do not direct any of our content specifically at children who are under 18 years of age. CouponPaste.com does not knowingly collect or solicit personal information from anyone under the age of 18 or knowingly allow such persons to register. If you are under 18, please do not send any information about yourself to us, including your name, address, telephone number, or email address. No one under age 18 is allowed to provide any personal information to or on CouponPaste.com. In the event that we learn that we have collected personal information from a child under age 18, we will delete that information as quickly as possible. If you believe that we might have any information from or about a child under 18, please contact us at contact@CouponPaste.com.

**Information Use**  
CouponPaste.com uses information obtained from its users and other visitors as described in this Policy, with the primary goal being to enhance user’s experiences on the CouponPaste.com website. We may use this information to deliver the services requested by users, to provide users with technical support, to enforce our Terms of Use, to communicate with users, to develop and display content and advertising tailored to your interests, and to manage our business operations. We may use information to perform other functions as otherwise described to you at the time of collection. CouponPaste.com may use information collected (without identifying you as an individual) to third-parties for purposes of aggregating data. We do not link aggregate user data with personally identifiable information.

Information that does not personally identify you as an individual that is collected by CouponPaste.com from the site (such as, by way of example, patterns of utilization) is exclusively owned by CouponPaste.com. This information can be utilized by CouponPaste.com in such manner as CouponPaste.com, in its sole discretion, deems appropriate.

**Communications with CouponPaste.com**  
CouponPaste.com will communicate with you through email and notices posted on the CouponPaste.com website. These include a series of up to 3 welcome emails that help inform new members about various features of the service. Please be aware that you will always receive certain emails from CouponPaste.com related to the proper functioning of your account, such as email notices alerting you when your registration is confirmed. Generally, you may not opt-out of these communications, which are not promotional in nature. If you do not wish to receive them, you have the option to deactivate your account. We will also communicate with you in response to your inquiries, to provide the services you request, and to manage your account. We will communicate with you by email or telephone, in accordance with your wishes.

CouponPaste.com may also send you promotional information unless you have opted out of receiving such information. Out of respect for your privacy, we present the option not to receive these types of communications. If you wish to opt-out of receiving promotional emails, please send a request to contact@CouponPaste.com.

**Information Sharing**  
CouponPaste.com takes the privacy of our users very seriously. We will never sell, rent, or otherwise provide your personally identifiable information to any third-parties for marketing purposes without your express permission. CouponPaste.com will only share collected information for the limited purposes set forth in this Privacy Policy.

It is possible that we may need to disclose personally identifiable information and/or non-personally-identifiable information if required to do so by law, or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with state and federal laws (such as U.S. Copyright Law) or respond to a court order, subpoena, search warrant or other legal process served on CouponPaste.com, its parent company, subsidiaries or affiliates.

CouponPaste.com also reserves the right to disclose personally identifiable information and/or non-personally-identifiable information that CouponPaste.com believes, in good faith, is appropriate or necessary to enforce our Terms of Use, take precautions against liability, to investigate and defend itself against any third-party claims or allegations, to assist government enforcement agencies, to protect the security or integrity of our website, and to protect the rights, property, or personal safety of CouponPaste.com, our members or others.

We may also share non-personally identifiable information with advertisers, business affiliates, publishers and other third parties for marketing purposes. We may provide aggregated data about the usage of our services to third-parties for such purposes as we deem, in our sole discretion, to be appropriate. We may segment our users by attributes such as geographic location, industry or trade, etc. If you would like to be excluded from the aggregated research or services based upon aggregated data about our users’ activities on the site, please email customer service at contact@CouponPaste.com.

Please be aware that CouponPaste.com is not responsible for any information you choose to share with others. While we take care not to share your personal information with third-parties, you must take responsibility for the content of material you make available to others online and through the CouponPaste.com site.

**Partnering with Other Organizations to Offer Combined Services**  
CouponPaste.com may from time to time partner with other online services to give you the combined results of both services. Whenever we offer such combined services it will be your choice to make use of the combined services or not. In these cases, your personally identifiable information will only be passed from CouponPaste.com to the partner if you choose to use the combined service.

**Links/Information Collected by Third-Party Sites**  
CouponPaste.com contains links to other third-party websites. Please be aware that third-party websites also may collect information from you. We are of course not responsible for the privacy practices of other websites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site to read the privacy statements of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information. This Privacy Policy applies solely to information collected by CouponPaste.com.

**Accessing and Changing Your Account Information**  
You can review the personal information you provided us and make any desired changes to the information, or to the settings for your CouponPaste.com account, at any time by logging in to your account on the CouponPaste.com website and editing the information on your profile page. We may retain certain data contributed by you if it may be necessary to prevent fraud or future abuse, or for legitimate business purposes, such as analysis of aggregated, non-personally-identifiable data, account recovery, or if required by law. All retained data will continue to be subject to the terms of the CouponPaste.com Privacy Policy that you have previously agreed to. To request that we close your account and remove your information from the CouponPaste.com service, please send your request to contact@CouponPaste.com. Please send your request using an email account that you have registered with CouponPaste.com under your name. You will receive a response to requests sent to contact@CouponPaste.com within 5 business days of our receiving it.

If you should make use of any communication features of the CouponPaste.com service to share information with other individuals on CouponPaste.com, however, (e.g., posting on bulletin boards, chat rooms, etc.) you generally cannot remove such communications.

**Security**  
The security of your personal information is important to us. CouponPaste.com takes appropriate precautions to protect our users’ information. Your account information is located on a secured server behind a firewall. However, no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. Accordingly, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to CouponPaste.com and you do so at your own risk. Once we receive your transmission of information, CouponPaste.com makes commercially reasonable efforts to ensure the security of our systems. However, please note that this is not a guarantee that such information may not be accessed, disclosed, altered, or destroyed by breach of any of our physical, technical, or managerial safeguards.

It is your responsibility to keep your password confidential. Do not share this information with anyone. If you are sharing a computer with anyone you should always choose to log out before leaving a website or service to protect access to your information from subsequent users.

If CouponPaste.com learns of a security systems breach, then we may attempt to notify you electronically so that you can take appropriate protective steps. CouponPaste.com may post a notice on the CouponPaste.com website if a security breach occurs. Depending on where you live, you may have a legal right to receive notice of a security breach in writing. To receive a free written notice of a security breach (or to withdraw your consent from receiving electronic notice) you should notify us via e-mail at contact@CouponPaste.com.

If you have any questions about the security of the CouponPaste.com website, please see our Security Response page.

**Special Note to International Users**  
The CouponPaste.com website and services are hosted in the United States and are intended for and directed to members in the United States. If you are a member accessing the CouponPaste.com website and services from the European Union, Asia, or any other region with laws or regulations governing personal data collection, use, and disclosure, that differ from United States laws, please be advised that through your continued use of the CouponPaste.com website and services, which are governed by U.S. law, this Privacy Policy, and our Terms of Use, you are transferring your personal information to the United States and you are expressly consenting to that transfer, and our collection and use of your personal information as described in this Privacy Policy.

**Merger, Sale, or Bankruptcy**  
In the event that CouponPaste.com is acquired by or merged with a third-party entity, we reserve the right, in any of these circumstances, to transfer or assign the information we have collected from our users and members as part of such merger, acquisition, sale, or other change of control. In the unlikely event of our bankruptcy, insolvency, reorganization, receivership, or assignment for the benefit of creditors, or the application of laws or equitable principles affecting creditors’ rights generally, we may not be able to control how your personal information is treated, transferred, or used.

**Terms of Use, Notices and Revisions**  
If you choose to visit CouponPaste.com, your visit and any dispute over privacy is subject to this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Use, including limitations on damages, and application of law of the state of Texas. We reserve the right to change our Privacy Policy and our Terms of Use at any time. Non-material changes and clarifications to our Privacy Policy will take effect immediately, and material changes to our Privacy Policy will take effect within 30 days of their posting on this site. If we make changes, we will post them and will indicate at the top of this page the policy’s effective date. We therefore encourage you to refer to this policy on an ongoing basis so that you understand our current privacy policy. Unless stated otherwise, our current privacy policy applies to all information that we have about you and your account.

**Questions or Comments**  
If you have questions or comments about this privacy policy, please email us at contact@CouponPaste.com.
